my first attempt with the plates
was i hooked up negative this end
positive that end and hoped it would
flow through
we got a very very minimal amount of gas
coming off the inside
face of negative only none of the other
plates not even positive was producing
well actually you could show that anyway
then
i took from negative here
and i went across to the n one so that
was positive negative that then becomes
what i found out that then becomes one
unit of two plates
that produce gas in the inside of there
tremendously
none of these produced still
similar fine mesh bubbling on this one
because we still have negative to it i
look to this
to the next we got fine bubbling in
between these
off that neutral plate off the inside a
positive
off the inside of negative and still the
fine bit on this end
i then went to center negative to center
i got production off two neutral plates
inside positive inside negative nothing
down this way
so i continued on down the way and it
diminished right out to nearly nothing
i looped me positive across to this side
i got gas in there which made one unit i
then looped it to this
to the next center the second plate up
fishing
i got gas in here none updating i move
to the center
i got gas on inside negative
two neutral plates on both sides and
inside
positive towards the negative none at
this end at all
i was then told that the place was too
small which i found out
my way it's not what i did then was take
me negative
from the end i put it in center
looped as i said before i'm taking
looped positive
each end the gas uh the the current flow
went both ways
and the gas ripped off every single one
of those plates on every side
she just roared in you couldn't solve
them that's
that's how i worked it to make the um
the beaver work
so let's see that it's under 15
as you can see oh that's right is it
i thought that in five
okay
they're still all coming away from all
those plates
yeah see she's opening up these plates
might be starting to clean until the sun
i'll look at the top of the bucket i'd
suggest that's what's happening
the main thing is producing on all of
the plaques and they're not connected
one plate uses a bit see that's going up
see that
this thing's got more peter 15 yeah you
look by the
seating end right right so that then why
or something something wrong with it
yeah well that doesn't surprise me i've
got a hold of it
okay
can you see that's the little bit can
you see that's coming off
it's going across all though isn't it
leave that breath check
my clean sides i think
there's no claim that it will and see
this way in center
two plates either way she's going either
way seat going that way
it's going that way it's going that way
it's going that way
all these are going coming away from all
surfaces
better don't have a
yeah small gas i mean that wire must be
losing today
so that's producing today's wires i'm
losing it
okay everywhere on this before when i
had them connected
and the thing every one of those ripped
out like just two together
okay 24 volts here now not 12.
we're going to try that out
you're not connected peter yes sir okay
every one of those plates are before me
are we right everyone
huh let me just go alligator clip
i'm still positive right you're positive
that one there
there you go
okay negative center
positive both ends
twice the guess i'll take it off here
why not let's try the amps can you do it
look at that if we pull in what's that
15.
this is about how it ripped out a bit
more than this with those other plates
better than that she'll contaminate our
bucket
yeah yes
that's the better one it's closer
than my eyes better
foreign silver
okay
okay see there's hardly anything off
those wire mesh outside
if you've got a solid outside you'll rip
off the solid outside
it's only really coming from negative
out
okay you're getting a fine one off the
positive but you need a solid
outside okay what's that
just on its own it's a new one yeah just
go to that way okay
that's not the inside but peter
if she stopped blowing things up
if we had a solid ring around the
outside the outside would produce
inwards that's only producing outward
seed
produced both ways
i'm in the right spot to make it no i'm
not there's not enough bubbles there
because if you're doing it this way is
can we put some water into here
to show also oh we can't we have nothing
actually we have yes we have voices
same stuff so if you're looking for a
reservoir or
a separator you can use the center even
though it's in the same order you can
use the setter
as a burn back
i've done it in the world the one i made
i done that i hooked the two rods into
there so that there's got enough gas
there to make it go bang
did we get that what was that okay
okay what we did here was took um some
of the
hydrogen oxygen gas under pressure off
into a very small welding tip
and we applied it to this side of the
brick
and as we come down with the tip
there was no splutterback the tip had a
very
fine little imploding blue flame
very very short imploding it was not
exploding
and we applied that down onto the brick
and what happened was the brick started
to swirl and gurgle up
and she blew a clean hole and this is
the back side
the gas come from that side come out
here there's no fluxing
nothing on there and then
we pulled the brick apart and as you can
see
she blew a clean hole straight through
the brick but turned this
brick into black
ceramic crystal that is harder harder
than the brick
there's no way to at least i don't know
how many times harder than the brick
and that heat come off the gas
which we're running in our motors and
what we are producing
here on the buckets the same gas
blew straight through and out there
as the implosion seems to be that while
it was inflating
and we pushed it down through the brick
she seems to pull up
the melted ceramic brick upwards
and twirl around the top not out the
bottom
on the top of the brick where you're on
the flame across
how fast would have you run that turn
the flame was probably taken across very
slowly
i didn't do this one my son done it he
played with all these
you just run it across slowly like that
and what she did was turn the
top of the brick glaze that was aimed
straight to the brick that's why she
spitted it out see on here
we had a high tensile headstone
welded as well you want to go
my son done this it also shows
brazing and solar
and this here is very very thick
stainless spring stainless that was
straight no flux no nothing no rod
straight to the
the gown um also
we blew just run the flame across and
she blew
straight through the gown we put the two
cut the two gal plates put them together
and you could solder them together it's
a complete neutral
flame so it was running off the same gas
i flew straight through that
but how are you producing it for
software what you do is come close yeah
off a battery all you do is come closer
or further away by only a degree on that
and you can either cut
by lifting it a fraction welding by
looking at it just a
fraction more or bring it a bit closer
and blow straight for a brief
overall between cutting welding and
blowing through a brick would be only
the distance of say an inch
what size um welding to
smallest we just well we had a big
welding set and we just got the smallest
big tip of it that's all we want we
didn't get a kickback
and you were
what was running the rover